KEIICHI KATSUNO

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

/ COFFEE ENTHUSIAST



PROFILE

A Software Developer and Coffee & Wine Enthusiast, originally from Japan. Passionate about business improvement with "Kaizen" that has a real influence on people's lives.

For the past 7 years, I have developed my ability in Marketing and Client Relationship Development in manufacturing in Japan, and Production Management in coffee in the UK and Colombia. Currently, I started my new challenge in IT in Melbourne such as Software Development. My all journey has always been shaping my personality and growing my confidence to survive in this real competitive world. Now, I deeply understand what I want to do / should do / will do in my life.

I place a high value on the **Integrity** in my life, having **Respect** to people and diverse cultures, and **Proactivity** and **Responsibility** in making my own decision.

EXPERIENCE

- AUSTRALIA

Frontend Web Developer - Freelance

June 2020 - Present

- as a Freelance. Melbourne
 - Web Site Development on Ruby on Rails
 - UI/UX Design

Coffee Production Assistant - Part-Time

October 2020 - Present [Specialty Coffee Roastery]

- at Small Batch Roasting Co., Melbourne

- Production Management of High Quality Coffee for The Local Market
- Production Quality Control & Asessment of Specialty Coffee

- COLOMBIA

Coffee Production Inspector - Internship

Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

- at InverCafé Ltda, Chinchiná

[Specialty Coffee Farm/Exporter]

• Production Quality Control & Asessment of Specialty Coffee

- THE UK

Coffee Production Manager - Full-Time

July 2018 - Sep 2019

- at The Roasting Shed Co, London

[Specialty Coffee Roastery]

- Production Roasting & Management of Specialty Coffee
- Local Market Research & Analysis of Needs-Meeting for Clients

- JAPAN

Clients Relationship Manager - Full-Time

Apr 2013 - July 2017 [Trading Company - Shosha]

- at Yuasa Trading Co, Tokyo

• Relationship Development with stakeholders, while ensuring successful sales, marketing and negotiation in the Japanese manufacturing industry, for the organisational sucess in a team

• Day to day **Account & Order Management** for my personal clients in the fast paced trade environment

EDUCATION

Software Development - Computer Science

Apr 2020 - Jun 2020

- at Le Wagon, Melbourne, Australia

- Web Development in Rails and Javascript
- UX/UI Design

Q Arabica Coffee Grader Training

Feb 2020 - Feb 2020

- at Japan Coffee Exchange, Shizuoka, Japan
 - General Knowledge of Coffee Production
 - Presice Coffee Production Assessment

Bachelor of Business Administration

Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

- at KinDai University, Osaka, Japan

Outside of study, I engaged in an American Football club where I learned:

- My own way of the Leadership & Team Management
- Logical Thinking for Organisational Success as well as Individual Success

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Problem solving by Logical Thinking
 Software Development in Ruby
- Clients Relationship Development
 UX/UI Design
- Sales & Marketing

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Weight Training, Meditation and Yoga
- American Football
- Non-Fiction (History, Anthropology, Biology, Nutrition, Psychology etc)
- Food & Beverage Industry (Third-Waved Coffee, Craft Beer and Wine)
- Information Technology (Software Development, BigData, AI, IoT etc)

REFFERENCES

Michael Allen

Operator of Small Batch Roasting Co. 040 146 8528

Paal Ringstad

Operator of Le Wagon Melbourne 042 396 7255



